A Guide to the Wade Hampton Frost Collection 1880-1938; 1938-1984
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 21 Nov. 1937, ALS (Box-folder 03-075)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 27 Dec. 1937, ALS (Box-folder 03-076)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 2 Jan. 1938, ALS (Box-folder 03-077)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 9 Jan. 1938, ALS (Box-folder 03-078)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 16 Jan. 1938, ALS (Box-folder 03-079)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH Jan. 1938, ALS (Box-folder 03-080)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 14 Feb. 1938, ALS (Box-folder 03-081)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO J. TRIPLETT HAXALL 21 March 1935, ALS (Box-folder 03-082)
- MEMO OF CONVERSATION WITH FREDERICK F. RUSSELL BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 8 July 1935, AM (Box-folder 03-083)
  ENVELOPE MARKED CONFIDENTIAL
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO THOMAS LOWNDES FROST 8 May 1922, TLS (Box-folder 03-084)
  THOMAS LOWNDES FROST: BROTHER OF WADE HAMPTON FROST
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO THOMAS LOWNDES FROST 17 May 1922, TLS (Box-folder 03-085)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO THOMAS LOWNDES FROST 28 May 1922, TLS (Box-folder 03-086)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO THOMAS LOWNDES FROST 28 May 1922, TL (Box-folder 03-087)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO THOMAS LOWNDES FROST 6 June 1922, TLS (Box-folder 03-088)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO THOMAS LOWNDES FROST 15 March 1923, AL (Box-folder 03-089)
  UNFINISHED LETTER; THOMAS LOWNDES FROST DIED THE NEXT DAY
- "SOME CONSIDERATIONS IN ESTIMATING THE SANITARY QUALITY OF WATER SUPPLIES" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 1915 Dec., reprint (EC) (Box-folder 04-001)
  REPRINTED FROM JOURNAL OF THE AMERICAN WATER WORKS ASSOCIATION WITH DISCUSSION
- "GENERAL PROGRAM FOR CONSERVATION OF PUBLIC HEALTH IN THE CIVIL POPULATION DURING THE WAR" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 1917, TM/AM (Box-folder 04-002)
  TYPEWRITTEN DRAFT WITH HANDWRITTEN CHANGES
- "AMERICAN RED CROSS AS A PUBLIC HEALTH AUXILIARY" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 1917, TM/AM (Box-folder 04-003)
- TITLE PAGES OF ARTICLES BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 1919-1939, reprints (EC) (Box-folder 04-004)
  IN PAPERS OF WADE HAMPTON FROST
- TITLE PAGE AND CHART FROM "STATISTICS OF INFLUENZA MORTALITY" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 12 March 1920, reprint (EC) (Box-folder 04-005)
  PUBLISHED IN PAPERS OF WADE HAMPTON FROST
- "NEW DEPARTMENT HEAD ADDED TO HOPKINS HYGIENE SCHOOL" c. 1921, newsclipping and EC (Box-folder 04-006)
  APPOINTMENT OF WADE HAMPTON FROST AT JOHNS HOPKINS
- ANNOUNCEMENT OF WADE HAMPTON FROST'S CUTTER LECTURES AT HARVARD MEDICAL SCHOOL 2/3 Feb. 1928, TD (Box-folder 04-007)
- NEWSPAPER ARTICLES FROM MANITOBA FREE PRESS RE: GORDON BELL MEMORIAL LECTURE BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 12/14 Dec. 1929, newsclipping and EC (Box-folder 04-008)
  PUBLISHED IN MANITOBA FREE PRESS
- "DR. W. H. FROST MADE HYGIENE SCHOOL DEAN" [1 July 1930], newsclipping (Box-folder 04-009)
  WADE HAMPTON FROST SUCCEEDS WILLIAM H. HOWELL AS DEAN OF JOHNS HOPKINS HYGIENE SCHOOL
- "AUTHORITATIVE STANDARDS AND ASSOCIATION POLICY" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 19 Dec. 1935, TM/AM (Box-folder 04-010)
- "OUTLOOK FOR THE ERADICATION OF TUBERCULOSIS" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 1935 Dec., reprint (Box-folder 04-011)
  "NOTE: ARTICLE MISSING; NOT PUBLISHED IN PAPERS OF WADE HAMPTON FROST; ORIGINAL GIVEN TO ERNEST L. STEBBINS, 07/29/72 "
- "HOW MUCH CONTROL OF TUBERCULOSIS?" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST Aug. 1937, reprint (Box-folder 04-012)
- "WHAT EVERY HEALTH OFFICER SHOULD KNOW" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST Oct. 1937, 2 TM (Box-folder 04-013)
  DRAFTS WITH HANDWRITTEN CHANGES
- "THE DOCTOR AND TUBERCULOSIS OF THE FUTURE" BY H. E. KLEINSCHMIDT WITH QUOTE BY WADE HAMPTON FROST Nov. 1937, reprint (Box-folder 04-014)
  PUBLISHED IN TUBERCULOSIS ABSTRACTS
- "AGE SELECTION OF MORTALITY FROM TUBERCULOSIS IN SUCCESSIVE DECADES" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST Nov. 1939, reprint (Box-folder 04-015)
- COMMONWEALTH FUND BOOK JACKETS: FROM "PAPERS OF WADE HAMPTON FROST" AND "SNOW ON CHOLERA 1936-1941, reprints (Box-folder 04-016)
- "THE ORIGINS OF THE FIRST SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLIC HEALTH AND THE EASTERN HEALTH DISTRICT IN BALTIMORE" BY HUNTINGTON WILLIAMS June-July 1961, reprint (Box-folder 04-017)
  PUBLISHED IN BALTIMORE HEALTH NEWS WITH AN INSCRIPTION TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST
- LETTERS TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST ON 10TH ANNIVERSARY OF THE DEATH OF WADE HAMPTON FROST 1948, leather-bound binder w/ TMS (Box-folder 04-018)
- EDITORIAL" ON WADE HAMPTON FROST Dec. 1950, reprint (Box-folder 04-019)
  PUBLISHED IN VIRGINIA MEDICAL MONTHLY
- MILBANK MEMORIAL FUND MEMORIAL BOOKLET TO WADE HAMPTON FROST 1938, AMS (Box-folder 04-020)
- OBITUARIES OF WADE HAMPTON FROST May 1938, newsclippings (Box-folder 04-021)
- OBITUARIES OF WADE HAMPTON FROST May 1938, newsclippings and EC (Box-folder 04-022)
- EDITORIAL BY JOHN W. OWENS ON DEATH OF WADE HAMPTON FROST 3 May 1938, newsclipping (Box-folder 04-023)
  OWENS WAS EDITOR-IN-CHIEF OF SUN & EVENING SUN OF BALTIMORE
- EDITORIAL ON BY DOUGLAS FREEMAN ON DEATH OF WADE HAMPTON FROST May 1938, newsclippings (Box-folder 04-024)
  EDITOR OF RICHMOND NEWS LEADER
- OBITUARY OF WADE HAMPTON FROST 7 May 1938, newsclipping (Box-folder 04-025)
  PUBLISHED IN FAUQUIER DEMOCRAT
- STATE OF NEW YORK BOARD OF HEALTH NEWS EDITORIAL ON DEATH OF WADE HAMPTON FROST 9 May 1938, TD (Box-folder 04-026)
- OBITUARY OF WADE HAMPTON FROST May 1938, newsclipping (Box-folder 04-027)
- EDITORIAL BY JOHN T. RAMEY ON DEATH OF WADE HAMPTON FROST May 1938, newsclipping (Box-folder 04-028)
- OBITUARIES OF WADE HAMPTON FROST May 1938, newsclippings (Box-folder 04-029)
- PARTIAL LIST OF CONTRIBUTORS TO FROST MEMORIAL FUND May 1938, TM/AM (Box-folder 04-030)
- EDITORIAL BY EDWIN S. GODFREY, JR. ON WADE HAMPTON FROST AND DRAFT June 1938, reprint/TM (Box-folder 04-031)
  PUBLISHED IN AMERICAN JOURNAL OF PUBLIC HEALTH
- COVER AND PHOTOGRAPHIC TRIBUTE TO WADE HAMPTON FROST Sept. 1938, TD/photo (Box-folder 04-032)
  FROM HUMAN BIOLOGY
- EDITORIAL ON DEATH OF WADE HAMPTON FROST WITH PHOTO AND LETTER FROM EDGAR ERSKINE HUME TO KENNETH F. MAXCY Nov. 1938, TM/TD (Box-folder 04-033)
- LETTER FROM ARCHIBALD S. DEAN TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 9 Nov. 1938, TMS (Box-folder 04-034)
  STATE OF NEW YORK DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH
- SEDGWICK MEMORIAL MEDAL AWARDED WADE HAMPTON FROST, M.D. Nov. 1938, TD (Box-folder 04-035)
- COMMONWEALTH FUND ANNUAL REPORT, 1938 PHOTOGRAPHIC TRIBUTE TO WADE HAMPTON FROST Jan. 1939, TD (Box-folder 04-036)
- "HOPKINS TO CONFER NEW DEGREE TODAY," [MASTER OF PUBLIC HEALTH DEGREE] 6 June 1939, newsclipping (Box-folder 04-037)
- PRESENTATION OF PORTRAIT OF WADE HAMPTON FROST TO JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY BY WILLIAM HENRY HOWELL 6 June 1939, TM (Box-folder 04-038)
- LETTER FROM HUNTINGTON WILLIAMS TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 27 Oct. 1939, TMS & EC (Box-folder 04-039)
  BALTIMORE CITY HEALTH DEPTARTMENT ANNUAL REPORT
- LETTER FROM J. A. DOULL TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST RE: DEDICATION TO WADE HAMPTON FROST BY DELTA OMEGA SOCIETY PUBLICATION July/Oct. 1940, 2 TMS (Box-folder 04-040)
  "PANUM'S ""OBSERVATIONS MADE DURING THE EPIDEMIC OF MEASLES ON THE FAROE ISLANDS IN 1846"
- REVIEW BY MAZYCK P. RAVENEL OF "PAPERS OF WADE HAMPTON FROST, M.D. A CONTRIBUTION TO EPIDEMIOLOGICAL METHOD." Nov. 1941, TD (Box-folder 04-041)
- EDITORIAL BY [HARRY S. MUSTARD], "PUBLIC HEALTH BALLOONS" Sept. 1941, TD (Box-folder 04-042)
- ARTICLE BY WILSON G. SMILLIE ET AL, "THE GREAT PIONEERS OF PUBLIC HEALTH IN AMERICA, 1610-1925" Sept. 1953, TD (Box-folder 04-043)
- LETTER FROM L.R. THOMPSON TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST RE: BRITISH MEDICAL JOURNAL TRIBUTE TO WADE HAMPTON FROST 28 Oct. 1942, TMS (Box-folder 04-044)
- JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY MEMORIAL TRIBUTE ON TWENTIETH ANNIVERSARY OF DEATH OF WADE HAMPTON FROST WITH LETTER FROM ERNEST L. STEBBINS 1 May 1958, TD; TM (Box-folder 04-045)
  INCLUDES NOTE BY [SUSAN FROST PARRISH]
- THIRD ANNUAL WADE HAMPTON FROST MEMORIAL LECTURE, "FROST REVISITED: THE MODERN EPIDEMIOLOGY OF TUPERCULOSIS" BY GEORGE W. COMSTOCK 1972-75, reprint and EC (Box-folder 04-046)
  APHA MEETINGS; INCLUDES NOTE BY [SUSAN FROST PARRISH]
- THE REED-FROST SYMPOSIUM ON BIOSTATISTICS AND EPIDEMIOLOGY AT THE JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY CENTENNIAL CELEBRATION 30 April 1976, pamphlet (Box-folder 04-047)
- PUBLIC HEALTH REPORTS, VOL. 95, NO. 5 Sept.-Oct. 1980, TD (Box-folder 04-048)
  WADE HAMPTON FROST ON COVER AND BRIEFLY DESCRIBED ON P. 410
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 1938, 4 AMS (Box-folder 04-049)
  RESTRICTED ACCESS
- DANVILLE MILITARY ACADEMY LATIN AWARD 1896, pin (Box-folder 05-001)
  PRESUMABLY AWARDED TO WADE HAMPTON FROST
- LETTER FROM JACK M. GWALTNEY, JR. TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH AND "GIVE US A SONG, BOYS" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 1913; 1976, 1 copy; 1 TL (Box-folder 05-002)
  CONTRIBUTION TO THE UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA SONGS AND YELLS PUBLISHED IN 1913
- UVA CERTIFICATE OF GRADUATION FROM ECONOMICS COURSE 1899, DS (Box-folder 05-003)
  AWARDED TO WADE HAMPTON FROST
- UVA CERTIFICATE OF GRADUATION FROM HISTORY COURSE 14 June 1899, DS (Box-folder 05-004)
- UVA CERTIFICATE OF GRADUATION FROM MATHEMATICS COURSE 14 June 1899, DS (Box-folder 05-005)
- UVA CERTIFICATE OF GRADUATION FROM COMPARATIVE ANATOMY COURSE 13 June 1900, DS (Box-folder 05-006)
- BIRTH CERTIFICATE OF WADE HAMPTON FROST, COPY MADE IN 1929 3 March 1880, DS (Box-folder 05-007)
- POEMS BY JOSEPH M. MARTIN, FOR SUSAN HAXALL FROST Feb. 1915, AN (Box-folder 05-008)
- BOOK OF COMMON PRAYER USED ON WEDDING DAY OF SUSAN HAXALL FROST AND WADE HAMPTON FROST 10 Feb. 1915, DS (Box-folder 05-009)
  CERTIFICATE OF MARRIAGE AND EPISCOPAL CHURCH PRAYERS AND SACRAMENTS
- FROST WEDDING ANNOUNCEMENT 10 Feb. 1915, D (Box-folder 05-010)
- "ANTI-MORTEM SONG TRIUMPHANT OF THE HEIR PRESUMPTIVE, NAPOLEONIC WILLIE" BY SUSAN HAXALL FROST 1920; 1984, 5 AN; 1 TNS (Box-folder 05-011)
  NOTE BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH FROM 1984 ATTACHED
- POEM BY SUSAN HAXALL FROST WRITTEN FOR NELL MACKENZIE TABB 1923, 3 AN (Box-folder 05-012)
- POEM BY LAURA ARMISTEAD CARTER FOR SUSAN HAXALL FROST 24 Nov. 1927, TN (Box-folder 05-013)
- CALLING CARD OF WADE HAMPTON FROST 1920s-30s, D (Box-folder 05-014)
- NEWSCLIPPING, RE: HAXALL'S KICK, YALE VS. PRINCETON, 1882 1930s, duplicate (Box-folder 05-015)
  PHOTOCOPY
- BOOKPLATES WITH FAMILY CREST OF WADE HAMPTON FROST ca. 1936; 1984, 1 D; 1 ANS (Box-folder 05-016)
- POEM BY LAURA ARMISTEAD CARTER FOR SUSAN HAXALL FROST 1938; 1975, 1 TNS; 1 ANS; 1 photocopy (Box-folder 05-017)
- DRAFT POEM FOR BY SUSAN HAXALL FROST FOR MRS. WILLIAM H. HOWELL nd, AN (Box-folder 05-018)
- "SOCIAL SERVICE IN TWELFTH CENTURY" BY MAIMONIDES nd, TMs (Box-folder 05-019)
  THE EIGHT DEGREES OF CHARITY
- TWO DRAFT POEMS BY SUSAN HAXALL FROST FOR 8OTH BIRTHDAY MAYPOLE PARTY 1932; 1984, 2 AN; 1 TNS (Box-folder 05-020)
- POEM BY MRS. HARTMAN HARRISON TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST AND SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1934; 1975, 2 TN; 1 ANS (Box-folder 05-021)
  "A POEM TO THE SUSANS FROST" WITH NOTE BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH FROM 1975"
- POEM BY HARRIET FROST SISTER OF WADE HAMPTON FROST, ON HIS DEATH 1938; 1984, 1 AN; 1 TNS (Box-folder 05-022)
  NOTE BY SUSAN F. PARRISH FROM 1984 ATTACHED
- NOTES ON SEDGWICK MEMORIAL MEDAL AWARDED TO WADE HAMPTON FROST IN 1938 1984, 1 TNS (Box-folder 05-023)
  NOTE BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH FROM 1984
- HAXALL REUNION 1949 1949; 1984, 1 D; 1 TNS (Box-folder 05-024)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN JULIUS P. BARCLAY, CURATOR OF RARE BOOKS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA LIBRARY AND SUSAN FROST PARRISH AND JOHN R. DUDLEY July 1975-January 1976, 9 TLS; 4 AM (copies); 2 photocopies (Box-folder 05-025)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN DOUGLAS W. TANNER, FIELD ARCHIVIST, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA LIBRARY, AND SUSAN FROST PARRISH Dec. 1975-June 1976, 3 ANS; 3 TLS (Box-folder 05-026)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN EDMUND BERKELEY, JR., CURATOR OF MANUSCRIPTS, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA LIBRARY AND SUSAN FROST PARRISH RE: JOHN S. MOSBY ITEMS July-Dec. 1975, 3 TMS (Box-folder 05-027)
- LETTER FROM JOHN S. MOSBY TO LENA NOLAND HAXALL 11 Sept. 1913, ALS (photocopy) (Box-folder 05-028)
- LETTER FROM JOHN S. MOSBY TO MRS. BOLLING HAXALL 21 Aug. 1914, 2 ALS (Box-folder 05-029)
- LETTER FROM JOHN S. MOSBY TO MRS. HAXALL 8 July 1915, ALS (Box-folder 05-030)
- LETTER FROM JOHN S. MOSBY TO MRS. BOLLING HAXALL 16 Oct. 1915, 2 ALS (copies) (Box-folder 05-031)
- LETTER FROM STUART MOSBY-COLEMAN TO LENA NOLAND HAXALL 11 May 1916, 2 TLS (copies) (Box-folder 05-032)
- LETTER FROM JOHN S. MOSBY TO MRS. BOLLING HAXALL 21 May 1916, 2 ALS (copies) (Box-folder 05-033)
- NEWSCLIPPINGS RE: JOHN S. MOSBY 1911; 1916, 2 D (copies) (Box-folder 05-034)
  MEMOIRS; OBITUARY
- NEWSCLIPPING RE: JOHN S. MOSBY nd, 2 photocopies (Box-folder 05-035)
  "VETERAN CONFEDERATE CAVALARY LEADER HERE"
- NEWSCLIPPING RE: JOHN S. MOSBY nd, photocopy (Box-folder 05-036)
  "COL. JOHN S. MOSBY DEAD"
- NEWSCLIPPING RE: JOHN S. MOSBY 1916, photocopy (Box-folder 05-037)
  "JOHN S. MOSBY NOTED SOUTHERN OFFICER DIES IN WASHINGTON, D.C."
- NEWSCLIPPING RE: JOHN S. MOSBY 1916, photocopy (Box-folder 05-038)
- NEWSCLIPPING RE: DEATH OF THOMAS LOWNDES FROST 16 March 1923, 1 clipping; 1 photocopy (Box-folder 05-039)
- ENVELOPE FROM [KENNETH F. MAXCY] TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 24 Oct. 1941, envelope only (Box-folder 05-040)
  *ENVELOPE ONLY--LETTER MISSING
- ENVELOPE FROM [CHARLES L. MINOR] TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 12 April 1918, envelope only (Box-folder 05-041)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AND SADIE R. HARVEY 22 Feb. 1986, photo 1 IPS 1 neg. B&W 2 7/8 X 3 3/8 (Box-folder 06-001)
  INSCRIBED BY SADIE R. HARVIE
- WADE HAMPTON FROST WITH STUDENT GROUP AT UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA 1898-1903, 1 photo; 2 negatives; B&W 5 X 5 (Box-folder 06-002)
- EXNING, RESIDENCE OF B. W. HAXALL, MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1900-1902, 4 photos 1 negative B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-003)
- VIEW NEAR MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1900-1902, 1 photo; 1 negative B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-004)
- BRIDGE OVER GOOSE CREEK, NEAR MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1900-1902, 2 photos; B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-005)
- MIDDLEBURG INN, MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1900-1902, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-006)
  [NOW THE RED FOX TAVERN]
- RESIDENCE OF MRS. ELLA MACKENZIE, MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1900-1902, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-007)
  "GLEN ORA" WITH NOTE BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH"
- BOLLING W. HAXALL AND PHILIP NOLAND, EAST WASHINGTON STREET, MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1900-1902, 1 photo; 1 negative B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-008)
- OAKHILL, FORMER HOME OF PRESIDENT MONROE, NOW OWNED BY SENATOR HENRY FAIRFAX, ALDIE VIRGINIA c. 1900-1902, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-009)
- THE MORAN HOUSE, MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1900-1902, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-010)
- THE CONFEDERATE HALL AND LIBRARY, MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1900-1902, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-011)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST, STUDIO PORTRAIT AS A YOUNG MAN c. 1901-1903, 2 photos; B&W 3 7/8 X 5 1/4; 6 3/4 X 9 1/2 (Box-folder 06-012)
- THOMAS LOWNDES FROST; MARTHA LOUISA FROST; SABRA JANE WALKER FROST AT MARSHALL, VIRGINIA c. 1905, 2 photos; 2 negatives B&W 5 3/4 X 6 1/2; 4 1/2 X 6 1/2 (Box-folder 06-013)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST IN MARSHALL, VIRGINIA c. 1905-1906, 2 photos; 2 negatives B&W 3 1/4 X 4 1/4; 4 X 5 (Box-folder 06-014)
- OFFICERS U.S.S. CHASE c. 1905-1908, 1 photo; 1 negative B&W 3 X 4 (Box-folder 06-015)
  INSCRIPTION BY WADE HAMPTON FROST
- SHORE LEAVE FROM THE U.S.S. ITASKA IN MARSEILLE 4 Sept. 1907, 2 photos; 1 negative B&W 3.5 X 5.5; 4 1/8 X 6.5 (Box-folder 06-017)
  INSCRIPTION BY WADE HAMPTON FROST; NOTE BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH FROM 1984 ATTACHED
- WADE HAMPTON FROST ABOARD U.S.S. ITASKA AT LE HAVRE 4 Aug. 1908, 3 photos; 4 negatives B&W 3.5 X 5.25; 4 7/8 X 6; 3 7/8 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-018)
  INSCRIPTION BY WADE HAMPTON FROST TO HARRIET FROST; NOTE BY SUSAN FROST PARRIS FROM 1984 ATTACHED
- WADE HAMPTON FROST, A FAMILY GATHERING, MARSHALL, VIRGINIA c. 1908, 3 photos; 2 negatives B&W 5 3/8 X 6 1/2 (2); 4 X 5 (Box-folder 06-019)
  NOTE BY SUSAN FROST PARRIS FROM 1984 ATTACHED
- WADE HAMPTON FROST c. 1908-1909, 1 photo; B&W 3.25 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-020)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST c. 1909, 1 photo; B&W 2.75 X 4.5 (Box-folder 06-021)
- SUSAN NOLAND HAXALL c. 1910, 1 photo; B&W 4.5 X 6.5 (Box-folder 06-022)
- OFFICE OF HENRY FROST ON GROUNDS OF HIS RESIDENCE AT MARSHALL, VIRGINIA c. 1910, 1 photo; 1 negative B&W 3.5 X 4.75 (Box-folder 06-023)
- SUSAN NOLAND HAXALL c. 1914, 2 photos; 1 negative B&W 3.25 X 4.75; 3.25 X 4.25 (Box-folder 06-024)
- EXNING, MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1910 - 1915, 7 photos B&W 2.75 X 4.5; 3.75 X 4.5 (Box-folder 06-025)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST WITH THREE BROTHERS, JAMES HENDERSON FROST, HENRY PINCKNEY FROST AND THOMAS LOWNDES FROST c. 1914, 2 photos B&W 3.25 X 4.25 (Box-folder 06-026)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST IN UNITED STATES PUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE UNIFORM c. 1915, 2 photos B&W 5 X 7 oval; 6.5 X 9.5 (Box-folder 06-027)
- SUSAN HAXALL FROST AT EXNING 1915-1916, 1 photo B&W 3.75 X 4.75 (Box-folder 06-028)
  INSCRIPTION BY MRS. BOLLING W. HAXALL
- DR. AND MRS. HENRY FROST, PARENTS OF WADE HAMPTON FROST IN MARSHALL, VIRGINIA c. 1916, 2 photos B&W 3 X 4; 5 X 7 (Box-folder 06-029)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST HOLDING FIRST-BORN CHILD, SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1916 June-July, 2 photos; 1 negative B&W 2.75 X 4.5; 5 X 7 (Box-folder 06-030)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST HOLDING FIRST-BORN CHILD, SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1916 June-July, 1 photo B&W 2.75 X 4.5 (Box-folder 06-031)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST HOLDING FIRST-BORN CHILD, SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1916 June-July, 2 photos B&W 2.75 X 4.5 (Box-folder 06-032)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST WITH GROWING BABY, SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1917, 1 photo B&W 3.25 X 4.25 (Box-folder 06-033)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST WHEN HE WAS A TUBERCULOSIS PATIENT IN CARE OF DR. CHARLES L. MINOR IN ASHEVILLE, NORTH CAROLINA Nov 1917 - April 1918, 3 photos; 2 negatives B&W 3.5 X 5.5; 4.5 X 6.5 (Box-folder 06-034)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST WITH BABY DAUGHTER, SUSAN FROST PARRISH c. 1918, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-035)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST HOLDING BABY DAUGHTER, SUSAN FROST PARRISH c. 1918, 1 photo B&W 2.75 X 4.5 (Box-folder 06-036)
- SUSAN HAXALL FROST, WADE HAMPTON FROST AND BOLLING W. BARTON AT EXNING c. 1918, 1 photo B&W 3.5 x 4.5 (Box-folder 06-037)
- DR. AND MRS. WILLIAM T. SEDGWICK n.d., 1 photo B&W 4 X 6; 1 card (Box-folder 06-038)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST READING TO DAUGHTER, SUSAN FROST PARRISH c. 1919, 1 photo B&W 2.75 X 4.5 (Box-folder 06-039)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST, LEWIS R. THOMPSON; HUGH DE VALIN; SUSAN FROST PARRISH; LOUISE HARRIS; MRS. LEWIS R. THOMPSON, MRS. THOMPSON, SR. c. 1920, 4 photos B&W 3 2.75 X 4.5; 1 5X 7 (Box-folder 06-040)
  NOTE BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH ATTACHED
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AND WILLIAM H. WELCH c. 1920, 2 photos; 2 negatives B&W 2 X 2; 5 X 7 (Box-folder 06-041)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST, SIR ARTHUR NEWSHOLME AND WILLIAM H. WELCH c. 1920, 2 photos; 1 negative; 1 xerox B&W 5 X 7; 2 X 2 (Box-folder 06-042)
- SIR ARTHUR NEWSHOLME, WILLIAM H. WELCH AND WADE HAMPTON FROST c. 1920, 1 photo B&W 2 X 2 (Box-folder 06-043)
- FIRST FACULTY OF JOHNS HOPKINS SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLICH HEALTH c. 1920, 1 xerox; 1 negative; 1 photo B&W 8 X 10 (Box-folder 06-044)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST WITH COLLEAGUE AT JOHNS HOPKINS SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLIC HEALTH n.d., 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-045)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST WITH DAUGHTER, SUSAN FROST PARRISH, AT EXNING, MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1920-1921, 1 photo B&W 2.5 X 3.5 (Box-folder 06-046)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AT TIME OF APPOINTMENT AS PROFESSOR OF EPIDEMIOLOGY, JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERISTY SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLIC HEALTH 1921, 3 photos B&W 1 5X 7; 2 4 X 6 (Box-folder 06-047)
- BOLLING W. BARTON AT EXNING IN MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1921, 1 photo B&W 2.5 X 4 (Box-folder 06-048)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST WITH GROUP FROM JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLIC HEALTH c. 1923, 2 photos B&W 5 X 7; 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-049)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AT EXNING, MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA n.d., 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 4.5 (Box-folder 06-050)
- FROST RESIDENCE AT 4710 KESWICK ROAD, ROLAND PARK, BALTIMORE c. 1926-1935, 1 photo B&W 2.5 X 4.25 (Box-folder 06-051)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST c. 1927, 2 photos B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 06-052)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST c. 1928, 2 photos; 1 negative B&W 2.75 X 5; 5 X 7 (Box-folder 06-053)
- HENRY FROST, FATHER OF WADE HAMPTON FROST c. 1861, 1 photo; B&W 2.5 X 4 (Box-folder 07-001)
- JAMES FENTON, CHARLES PORTER, GEORGE BUCHAN, ROBERT RILEY AND WADE HAMPTON FROST c. 1930-1933, 1 newsclipping photograph (Box-folder 07-002)
  "BRITISH HEALTH MEN VISITING HERE"
- WADE HAMPTON FROST 24 April 1931, 2 photos; 1 negative B&W 2.25 X 3.25; 5 X 7 (Box-folder 07-003)
  INSCRIPTION BY YAZO TOKYAMA
- WADE HAMPTON FROST 24 April 1931, 1 photo B&W 2.25 X 4.25 (Box-folder 07-004)
  INSCRIPTION BY YAZO TOKYAMA; NOTE BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH FROM 1981 ATTACHED
- GARRIDO AND MRS. GARRIDO MORALES 1931, 1 photo B&W 2.5 x 4.25 (Box-folder 07-005)
  INSCRIPTION BY DR. AND MRS. GARRIDO MORALES; NOTE BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH FROM 1984 ATTACHED
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AT EXNING, MIDDLEBURG, VIRGINIA c. 1932, 1 photo B&W 2.75 x 4.25 (Box-folder 07-006)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST WITH GROUP FROM JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLIC HEALTH c. 1932-1936, 1 photo B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 07-007)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST WITH COLLEAGUES c. 1932-1936, 1 photo B&W 2.75 X 4.5 (Box-folder 07-008)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST BY FREDERIC FARLEY 9 Dec. 1933, 1 photo of pencil sketch 8 x 10 (Box-folder 07-009)
- WILLIAM T. SEDGWICK c. 1918, 1 photo B&W 5 X 8 (Box-folder 07-010)
- JOSEPH S. AMES, PRESIDENT, JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY 17 June 1935, 1 photo B&W 8 X 10 (Box-folder 07-011)
  INSCRIPTION BY JOSEPH S. AMES
- WADE HAMPTON FROST RESIDENCE IN BALTIMORE 1935 - c. 1950's, 10 photos; 3 negatives B&W 3.25 X 5.25 (Box-folder 07-012)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AND SUSAN HAXALL FROST IN BALTIMORE 1935, 2 photos; 1 negative B&W 3.25 X 5.25 (Box-folder 07-013)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST PORTRAIT PHOTOGRAPH WIDELY USED POSTHUMOUSLY c. 1935-37, 2 photos; B&W 8 X 10 (Box-folder 07-014)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST c. 1935-37, 1 negative (Box-folder 07-015)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AND LOWELL REED c. 1936, 2 photos; 1 negative B&W 2.75 X 4.25; 5 X 7 (Box-folder 07-016)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST c. 1936, 2 photos; 1 negative B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 07-017)
- LOWELL J. REED, WADE HAMPTON FROST, MARGARET MERRILL AND MRS. MOLLIE REED c. 1937, 1 photo B&W 2.75 X 4.5 (Box-folder 07-018)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST LECTURING AT JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLIC HEALTH c. 1937, 2 photos; 1 negative B&B&W 3.75 X 5.25 (Box-folder 07-019)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST LECTURING AT JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLIC HEALTH c. 1937, 1 photo; 1 negative B&W 3.75 x 5.25 (Box-folder 07-020)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AT STEVENSON, MARYLAND Oct. 1937, 4 photos; 1 negative B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 07-021)
- CHRISTMAS TREE AT 508 WOODLAWN RD. 25 Dec. 1937, 1 photo B&W 3.75 X 5.25 (Box-folder 07-022)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AND SUSAN FROST PARRISH 25 Dec. 1937, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 07-023)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AND SUSAN FROST PARRISH 25 Dec. 1937, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 07-024)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST 25 Dec. 1937, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.5 (Box-folder 07-025)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST; ELIZABETH EARLE 25 Dec. 1937, 1 photo; 1 photo fragment B&W 3.25 X 4.5 (Box-folder 07-026)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AND RICHARD A. JAMISON 25 Dec. 1937, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.25 (Box-folder 07-027)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST 25 Dec. 1937, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.25 (Box-folder 07-028)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST, RICHARD A. JAMISON AND LOUSE TRIPLETT HAXALL HARRIS 25 Dec. 1937, 1 photo (Box-folder 07-029)
- SUSAN HAXALL FROST AND J. MORRISON HARRIS 25 Dec. 1937, 1 photo (Box-folder 07-030)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST c. 1937-1938, 5 photos B&W 2.5 X 3.5 (Box-folder 07-031)
- SUSAN HAXALL FROST c. 1939, 1 photo (Box-folder 07-032)